There is a woman there! You keep seeing dead people in your dream all the time.
Please, come out.
Man of God, help me. I am the woman who always sees dead people in the dream.
I always see dead people, and that is why I came here.
You don't want to die?
I don't want to die now, my children are still small. I'm a widow.
Forget about that.
I don't want to die.
If you are ready to live for God, you will not die.
I am living for God, Man of God.
You have been living for God? Ok, it's alright.
If you have been living for God, you would not be afraid of death. Over there is our home.
Who will take care of my children that are here, if I go there?
Where?
The place you are talking about now.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The place I am talking about now?
You don't know the place?
I know. If I'm saying...
No, no. The place I'm talking about - as if I'm the only person that knows the place.
Does it mean you don't know the place?
I know the place, Man of God.
Where is the place?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Where is the place, if you know the placet?
It's too early for me to go there now.
- It's too early for you to go there?
- Now.
Are you saying it was too early for Jesus to go there at 33?
How old are you now?
No, His own was a...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
His own was a divine something.
- Your own is what?
- His was predicted.
His own was divine something and it was for a purpose.
What of your own?
I don't know now.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I said that I'm a widow and my children are very small.
It's like you know death is coming.
That is the question. Answer me.
It's because I am seeing dead people.
It's not good for someone living here to be associating with dead people while sleeping.
So, you have denied your husband?
That's not what the Bible says.
The Bible says that after death, there is no husband and wife again.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I know you have some splendour, wealth you don't just want to leave behind.
It's just because of my children.
If they were grown up, I won't bother.
We will ask God.
If you are going to live for Him, this death, we will remove it.
But if you are not ready to live for Him...
I am ready to live for Him all the days of my life, Man of God.
TT: Anonymous
RV: Mel Flowers 12/01/2019